It's cute.
かわいいよ
Well then, take a step to make yourself look full,
じゃあ、一歩満腹よく見える浮かしをして、
Well then, let's go out, okay?
じゃあ、出てみようか、そりゃね
No, it's okay, Yui
いや、大丈夫、結
構
I'll put it in.
入 れます
It's left behind.
残っちゃったですね
You don't have to cut it out for a while,
ちょっと、抜き切んなくていいから、
Let's put it in and take it out below.
下に出し入れしてみよう
There, there, put the way to dispose of it.
そこ、そこ、捨て方入れって
There are many.
多いですよ
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すごい
It's delicious.
うまいよ
Are there that many?
そんなにあるの?
interesting.
面白い
Interesting, interesting.
面白い、面白い
So let's include that as well.
じゃあ、それも入れてみようか
No, it doesn't hurt.
いやだ、痛くない
Wait, no?
ちょっと、ない?
Oh, don't hide it too much.
あ、あんま隠さないで
It is written in the summary.
あらわせに書いてある
Pretty clear.
結構、鮮明
Wow, it looks really close up.
え、めっちゃなんか、アップに見えるんですね
Put it in and take it out.
出 し入れして
Slowly, slowly.
ゆっくり、ゆっくり
Well then, let's put it in slowly.
じゃあ、ゆっくり入れてみようか
Yes, thank you very much.
はい、ありがとうございました
yes.
はい